localmedicalguide.com 2010-09-30

# Local Medical Guide | Privacy Policy

**How do we use Information**

We information can be obtain on your own questions about the products, our programs and services to meet your requirements for proposals, and give you other products, programs or services that? we believe that you.

Sometimes use this information to contact you, because you will be notified when one of our contests or when we won the modified subscriber agreements, to satisfy a request by you for an online newsletter, or contact your account with us.

We use the information for you on the other, then we send them gifts or cards. From time to time we may use this information for products, our programs or services they offer.

If you choose to submit content for publication (eg, a? letter to our editors ), you may include your name, publish the names of instant messaging, and other information you provide.

The data will be combined with our forums and online communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these forums and online communities, and from time to time to give you products, programs or services.

We may use personal information we collect to improve the design and content of our publications and web sites and allow us to customize your experience on the Internet. We can use this information as a whole, to analyze the use of space and offer you products, programs or services.

We will only share information when we say that the legislature should not ask, for example under a court order or subpoena. We may disclose such information in response to a question by law enforcement.

Agents and contractors of year species have access to personal information needed to obtain this information in a manner consistent with this policy on privacy, for example, does not use the information other than the performance of agencies responsible for implementation of VAT Time

We may use your personal information to other tax offices time to transfer the internal management and administrative purposes. Your personal information is other local Time Inc, which is necessary for the performance or the performance of our contractual obligations to you or shipped to your advantage. Transfer of personal data may also be made where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defend legal claims.

Although we take appropriate measures must be protected from unauthorized disclosure of information, we can not guarantee that personal data collected will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this statement.  
Accidental cause information may, for example, if the third evil, seeking the identity of the site for access to personal information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

**Collection of information through websites and third Sponsors**

Some our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may differ from us. Should the private lives of the other areas mentioned in the notes, after we have no control over the information collected will be transmitted to or from such third parties.

Time Inc. sites sometimes offer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, editorial features, or other activities or promotions that are sponsored or owned by, or presented with sponsorship identified third parties. By participating in these activities, or agreements with the personal information you may voluntarily submit such to the website of Time Inc and the third will be available.  
Time Inc. has no control over the use of third? of information.

Time Inc. sites may use reputable third parties to make or serve the advertisements you see on their websites and conduct research on advertising. This policy of privacy protection does not cover the use of such information to third parties by you or other methods used may be recorded) to collect information (such as cookies, web beacons and clear gifs. For more information on the use of This third
